Hey you. You left laundry in the dryer.
Hey you. 你把衣服留在供干机里了.
You're supposed to do the whole load yourself- start to finish.
你应该自己把这事从头至尾的全部做完.
I forgot. I'm sorry.
我忘了. 对不起.
So, what do you think of Dad's plans?
那么, 你对爸爸的打算怎么看?
It's cool I guess. If he wants to do it.
我觉得不错. 如果他希望那么做.
Why now?
为什么是现在?
Well, it happens when you make a name for yourself.
Well, 一个人成名以后这些事就会发生.
But he was just doing his job, right?
可他只是在格尽职守, 不是吗?
Pretty funny, huh?
很有趣, huh?
He was doing it so well, he's on the news.
他干得很好, 都上新闻了.
Will we be no the news?
我们会上新闻吗?
Yes, I think so. at some point.
会的, 我想会的.在某个时刻.
And some people may ask you a lot of questions.
而且有些人或许会问你许多问题.
You have to decide for yourself whether to answer them.
你得自己决定是否回答.
But you can always come to us and talk about it.
但是你总是可以来找我们谈谈的.
You know that, right?
你是知道的, 对吗?
Yeah. I just hope they don't get totally invasive.
对. 我只希望他们对我们的干扰不要太大.
We'll keep things as normal as possible for ourselves.
我们将尽力使一切保持正常.
At least here at home.
至少在家里.
Speaking of which, I am going to the pool tomorrow morning.
说到这个, 我明天早上打算去游泳.
Do you want to go swimming with me?
你想和我一起去游泳吗?
Yes! Oh. What time?
好啊! Oh. 什么时候?
Early, early, early. Oh, come on. It'll be fun.
很早, 很早, 很早. Oh, 来吧, 会很有趣的.
We can be in the water by 7:30 in the morning.
我们可以在早晨7点半前下水.
Mom, you're crazy.
妈妈, 你疯了.
Don't make me go all by myself.
别让我一个人去吧.
Leave at ten and then I'll go with you.
10点出发我就跟你去.
Ten! Eight o'clock.
10点! 8点吧.
Nine.
9点.
Eight-thirty. Final offer.
8点半. 不能再晚了.
And breakfast at the Tasty Diner afterwards.
然后在Tasty Diner吃早饭.
Deal.
一言为定.
Good. Sleep tight.
好. 睡个好觉.